# **SONIA DUA**

- In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sonia-dua-4aa980130
- ②: soniadua7913@gmail.com 7986-974-880 1414-G Park View Apt,Gautum Buddh Nagar U.P-201301

# **SKILLS**

- 1. JavaScript
- 2. Node.js
- 3. Angular 2+
- 4. ES6
- 5. Express.JS
- 6. MongoDB
- 8. Microservices
- 9. CRON
- 10. HTML/CSS/BOOTSTRAP

#### **TOOLS**

- 1.Git
- 2. Jira
- 3. ASANA

# **CERTIFICATION**

- Server-side Development with NodeJS, Express and MongoDB
  - -- Coursera (11/2019)
- 2. Front-End JavaScript Frameworks: Angular -- Coursera (08/2019)

#### **INTEREST**

- 1. Reading Blogs and articles
- 2. Problem Solving
- 3. Object Oriented Programming

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a dedicated team player with valuable experience in MEAN Stack Technologies like Angular 8, NodeJs , JavaScript, MongoDB, Express and Micro-service architechture.

I believe my previous experience and ability to quickly pickup new skills will help both the organization I work for and myself to scale up.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Biz2Credit - Software Developer

Noida, Uttar Pradesh - 06/2019 - Current

HSBC-US

06/2019 - Current

- 1. I have been working as a Core member of HSBC-US Project (A lending platform for business)
- 2. Worked on Bank Statement Analyser, IRS, NOI etc. Micro-services as well as integrated Third Party Modules like Experian, Fraud Check etc using MEAN Stack.

# VenturePact LLC - Associate Software Developer

Jalandhar, Punjab - 01/2018-06/2019

Neta-App

04/2018-06/2019

- 1. Worked on Neta App which describe about the Leaders report card as well as integrated results of upcoming election on the basis of prediction of candidates reviews and their rating which they can give in the platform by login using their number as well as check the results of MP or MLA using their GeoLocation or by input the location they want to know about.
- 2. Technologies Used: Angular 4, Angular 6
- Resume Builder

01/2018-04/2018

- 1. Worked on Resume Builder which helps user to create the resume from number of templates available and can enter the details they want to show as a person l or professional part for career builder.
- 2. Technologies Used: Javascript, Html/CSS, Bootstrap

### **EDUCATION**

1. Lovely Professional University - JALANDHAR B.Tech(CSE) - (8.03) CGPA - May/2018

2. Bal Vidya Mandir Senior Secondary School - LUCKNOW 10+2 - CBSE (7.52) CGPA - APRIL/2014

3. Bal Vidya Mandir Senior Secondary School - LUCKNOW High School - CBSE (7.40) CGPA - APRIL/2012